<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

	<ResearchTabDef>
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenReTab</defName>
		<label>Skaven</label>
	</ResearchTabDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef Name="RH_TET_Skaven_Research" Abstract="True">
		<requiredResearchBuilding>RH_TET_Skaven_ResearchBench</requiredResearchBuilding>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tab>RH_TET_SkavenReTab</tab>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectTagDef>
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</defName>
	</ResearchProjectTagDef>

	<!-- Column 1 -->
 
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_Art</defName>
		<label>Art</label>
		<description>Allows colonists to make skaven themed art statues.</description>
		<baseCost>250</baseCost>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<researchViewX>0.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponryRanged_Basic</defName>
		<label>basic ranged weaponry</label>
		<description>Unlocks the simplest of ranged weapons used by the skaven, if one could truly call a sling a weapon.\n\nBasic, ineffective, but useful nonetheless. Especially when fielded in significant numbers, the sling is by far the most numerous ranged weapon employed in all of Skavendom. Little more than a scrap of cloth on a string, these simple tools are typically fielded in the dozens or hundreds, depending on the warband's size. While a single rock flung by these devices seems harmless, a volley of them can prove devastating by comparison.</description>
		<baseCost>100</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<researchViewX>0.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.75</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_Plants</defName>
		<label>agriculture</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to grow skaven specific plants. These are typically less healthy plants, but that grow relatively quickly and have high yields; if they're food plants.</description>
		<baseCost>100</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<researchViewX>0.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1.5</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponryMelee_Basic</defName>
		<label>basic melee weaponry</label>
		<description>Unlocks simple skaven melee weapons.\n\nThese are often little more than makeshift armaments fashioned from scrap parts. To the Skaven, if it has a part you can hold and another bit you could feasibly deal damage with, it's good enough. With rusted metal and rotted wood, most sentient folk would scarcely consider these effective weapons. In the Under-Empire, however, the quality of the weapon matters less than the quantity of weapons they can field.</description>
		<baseCost>300</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<researchViewX>0.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2.25</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_Cooking</defName>
		<label>food stuffs</label>
		<description>Allows skaven to make food related things, such as a feed hopper.</description>
		<baseCost>500</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<researchViewX>0.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenApparel_Basic</defName>
		<label>basic apparel</label>
		<description>Teaches your skaven how to fashion basic rag clothes out of whatever scraps they can find.\n\nThese particular clothes are by far the most numerous in the Under-Empire, being little more than reused cloth cut and sewn into what one could vaguely describe as 'clothing'. Such garments typically hint towards the rank of the ratman wearing it. The less they're wearing, the lower on the social ladder they tend to be.</description>
		<baseCost>200</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<researchViewX>0.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.75</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_Medicine</defName>
		<label>medicine</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to for skaven to build a drug making table (Moulder Work Bench), and to craft medicine (as well as other drugs) there.\n\nInjury is common in the warrens, and so is infection. Finding a way to keep their minions healthy is important to some skaven leaders, though certainly not all of them.</description>
		<baseCost>750</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<researchViewX>0.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>4.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_CrudeStructure</defName>
		<label>crude structure</label>
		<description>Allows skaven to build crude structures that are cheap, fast to build, and that suit their style and needs. Crude wooden floors, wall vents, crude wood or metal walls, and walls made of dung.</description>
		<baseCost>450</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<researchViewX>0.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>5.15</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenFurniture</defName>
		<label>furniture</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to build skaven furniture and work benches.\n\nFurniture in the Under-Empire is an uncommon sight, and just like all things made by the skaven, often composed of scrap materials. The skaven who use them care little about the craftmanship involved in the creation of such furnishings so long as it provides a use, however briefly.</description>
		<baseCost>250</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<researchViewX>0.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>5.75</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<!-- Column 2 -->
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponryRanged_Improved</defName>
		<label>advanced ranged weaponry</label>
		<description>Unlocks advanced skaven ranged weapons not employed by any particular clan.\n\nSkavendom rarely if ever employs the use of archery. The materials needed to craft bows, crossbows, bolts, and arrows simply aren't common enough in the world below to justify their use, especially with the inventions of Skryre satisfying the need for potent ranged firepower. Still, it's not unheard of for a skaven to repurpose the designs of man-things or dwarf-things to create their own simple crossbow design. If nothing else, doing so at least gives the ratmen more of a use for scavenged quarrels and bolts.</description>
		<baseCost>450</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponryRanged_Basic</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>1.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.75</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponryMelee_Improved</defName>
		<label>improved melee weaponry</label>
		<description>Unlocks advanced skaven melee weapons used by countless different clans.\n\nThese particular weapons mark the point where craftsmanship actually becomes somewhat necessary for the skaven. As a result, these particular weapons are often reserved for the elite members of the Under-Empire's forces, such as the infamous Stormvermin.</description>
		<baseCost>500</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponryMelee_Basic</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>1.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2.25</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenApparel_Armour</defName>
		<label>basic armor</label>
		<description>Allows for the creation of basic skaven armors.\n\nTrue protective gear is a luxury rarely afforded to most skaven, as a single clanrat is often far cheaper than even a simple piece of chainmail. When they are afforded such things, their armors are cobbled together from disparate scrap parts just as their weapons often are. Still, they prove more effective than nothing, and any lowly skaven would gladly kill their kin to have such luxuries for themselves.</description>
		<baseCost>800</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenApparel_Basic</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>1.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenApparel_Advanced</defName>
		<label>advanced apparel</label>
		<description>Teaches your skaven the basic tailoring techniques needed to create more elaborate clothing than simple rags.\n\nTo skaven in high standing, elaborate clothes denote social status. The Grey Seers themselves tend to favour patchwork robes that clothe them from neck to foot, providing ample coverage without impeding their movement. Mobility is crucial for the Grey Seers, as armor interferes with their ability to channel magical energy.</description>
		<baseCost>350</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenApparel_Basic</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>1.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.75</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_Furniture_Recreation</defName>
		<label>recreation</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to build skaven related recreation items.\n\nGiven the large numbers of skaven typically around, having something to do to keep them happy is important. Obnoxious gong music can frequently be heard droning through the skaven warrens as skaven seeking something to do bang on them.</description>
		<baseCost>250</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenFurniture</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>1.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>4.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenSecurity</defName>
		<label>security</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to build skaven defensive buildings, starting with the skaven pavise shield.\n\nThese simple defenses are most frequently employed by Clan Skryre's famous Warplock Jezzail weapon teams, acting to both protect them from retaliatory weapons fire and to stabilize the extraordinarily long barrels employed by them. Even without said weapon to accompany it, all Skaven would happily take this flimsy cover over being out in the open.</description>
		<baseCost>250</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<researchViewX>1.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>5.10</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenFurniture_Advanced</defName>
		<label>advanced furniture</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to build larger skaven furniture.\n\nFurniture in the Under-Empire is an uncommon sight, and just like all things made by the skaven, often composed of scrap materials. The skaven who use them care little about the craftmanship involved in the creation of such furnishings so long as it provides a use, however briefly.</description>
		<baseCost>350</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenFurniture</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>1.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>5.75</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<!-- Column 3 -->
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_BlackPowder</defName>
		<label>Black Powder</label>
		<description>Allows skaven to make black powder. Mineable saltpeter and sulfur can then be combined with wood for charcoal at a munitions bench, to be turned into black powder. Black powder is used to make rounds for black powder warmachines.\n\nKnowledge of black powder allows skaven to progress to more advanced warpstone based technologies.</description>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponryRanged_Improved</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>2.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.75</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenApparel_ArmourHeavy</defName>
		<label>advanced armour</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to forge Stormvermin armour, the most protective gear afforded to the rank-and-file of the Under-Empire's elite.\n\nStormvermin plate stands among the most effective armour that the Lords Of Decay have to offer their elite soldiers, with variants employed by even most warlords. Most clanrats are too small or weak to use these heavy suits of plate, however, as only the brutal and imposing black-furs are permitted to stand among the elite ranks of the Stormvermin.</description>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenApparel_Armour</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>2.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_ConstructionAdvanced</defName>
		<label>advanced construction</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to make a tunnel to the under-way.\n\nThe under-way is a vast network of underground tunnels. Skaven travel those routes, and infest the entire globe via the endless maze of tunnels.\n\nBe wary, building this will encourage the treacherous Under Empire to betray and attack you via the under-way.</description>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenFurniture_Advanced</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>3.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>5.6</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<!-- Column 4 -->

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponsRanged_Eshin</defName>
		<label>Eshin ranged weaponry</label>
		<description>Unlocks the creation of ranged weapons employed by the secretive Clan Eshin.\n\nThe throwing stars used by Clan Eshin have proven their lethality ever since the Clan's return from the Far East. Most Night Runners and Gutter Runners will carry at least a few such stars, often dripping with poison, and use them to kill or weaken lightly-armored opponents at short range.</description>
		<baseCost>350</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponryRanged_Improved</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>3.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.0</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenSkryreWeaponry</defName>
		<label>Skryre melee weaponry</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to make the rarely used, but often effective melee weapons employed by Clan Skryre.\n\nClan Skryre is known far more for their weapons of war than they are for their skill at arms. Loathe as they are to fight in close proximity, the engineers of Clan Skryre have a few weapon designs to give them an edge if forced into close-quarters combat.</description>
		<baseCost>800</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponryMelee_Improved</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>3.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenEshinGear</defName>
		<label>Eshin gear</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to make the stealth related gear of Clan Eshin.\n\nClan Eshin is known for the arts of stealth, deception, assassination, and the like. Their gear is there to help them facilitate those aims.</description>
		<baseCost>300</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenApparel_Armour</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>3.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2.25</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_MoulderEnhancements</defName>
		<label>Moulder body enhancements</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to make Moulder experimental items for enhancing their warbeasts. Unlocks prosthetic recipes for rat ogres such as steel denture, steel plates, blade arms, and steel legs.\n\n"An artist never truly finishes his work. He merely abandons it." This idiom also applies to the fleshcrafters of Clan Moulder, who are never truly satisfied with the lethality of their warbeasts. There's always an improvement to be made, even if it means grafting chunks of steel or warpstone to the limbs of rat ogres to improve their performance in combat. Of course if a rat ogre loses a limb in combat naturally, prosthetics like this ensure that the beast remains useful.</description>
		<baseCost>1100</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<researchViewX>3.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenSecurity_Skryre</defName>
		<label>Skryre security</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to build Skryre skaven defensive (and offensive) buildings.\n\nClan Skryre's primary market may be in the realm of weapons built for massed warfare, but their Warlock Engineers are still keenly aware of the more personal market for defensive weaponry.</description>
		<baseCost>750</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenSecurity</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>3.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>4.25</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenFurniture_Skryre</defName>
		<label>Skryre buildings</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to build a few Skryre buildings that may seem lacking in the lethality department, but still have their use.\n\nClan Skryre has their own fair share of project failures, the Pipes of Piebald were infamously the result of a botched attempt to build a death ray. Some such designs, like the Warp Brazier, still find their niche in Skavendom.</description>
		<baseCost>525</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenFurniture_Advanced</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>3.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>5.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<!-- Column 5 -->

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponsRanged_Skryre</defName>
		<label>Skryre ranged weaponry</label>
		<description>Unlocks the creation of basic Skryre weaponry.\n\nWarplock and poison wind weapons stand among Skryre's earliest and most effective designs, with the added bonus of being small enough for a single skaven to carry. They both prove devastating on the battlefield, and have a lasting impact on any who somehow survive the ordeal.</description>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_BlackPowder</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>4.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.0</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenMoulderWeaponry_Basic</defName>
		<label>Moulder melee weaponry</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to craft the tools employed by Clan Moulder to tame their war beasts, or occasionally to capture new test subjects.\n\nPerhaps the only incarnation of non-lethal weaponry in the entirety of skavendom, as their intent is less to kill than it is to incapacitate. These tools of pain and restraint are still brutal and sadistic by any measure.</description>
		<baseCost>800</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponryMelee_Improved</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>4.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenMoulderGear</defName>
		<label>Moulder gear</label>
		<description>Unlocks the armor sets used by the packmasters of Clan Moulder.\n\nThe beasts of Clan Moulder are infamously lethal, bred and moulded into killing machines from the moment the clan lays their claws on them. Any time one such beast gets loose, the casualties of their rampage can prove too excessive even by skaven standards. Thus many Master Moulders give their packmasters a modicum of protection, hoping to reduce that number to more tolerable levels.</description>
		<baseCost>700</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenApparel_Armour</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>4.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2.25</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenMoulderBase</defName>
		<label>moulder experiments</label>
		<description>Unlocks the first step into Clan Moulder's fiendish practice of fleshcraft.\n\nMoulder may have more mundane methods of developing ever more lethal war beasts, like selective breeding and obedience training, but to the short-lived and impatient skaven that's often considered far too slow. Why wait for a newborn wolf rat to reach adulthood when you can force years worth of it's growth into a single afternoon?</description>
		<baseCost>750</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_MoulderEnhancements</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>4.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenSecurity_SkryreAdvanced</defName>
		<label>Skryre security advanced</label>
		<description>Unlocks Skryre's famous warp-lightning technology. Both the cannons themselves, and the batteries that power them.\n\nThe warp-lightning cannon stands among Clan Skryre's most ingenius designs, melding both magic and science into one devastating weapon. While Skryre's other weapons often need ammunition or fuel, these cannons channel massive amounts of raw energy into a single blast of pure warp-lightning.</description>
		<baseCost>2500</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenSecurity_Skryre</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>4.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>4.25</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_Magic</defName>
		<label>Basic Magic Items</label>
		<description>Allows skaven seers to craft basic magic items.</description>
		<baseCost>2500</baseCost>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<researchViewX>4.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>5.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>


	<!-- Column 6 -->

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponsRanged_SkryreAdvanced</defName>
		<label>advanced Skryre ranged weaponry</label>
		<description>Unlocks the creation of Skryre's advanced weapon designs.\n\nThese particular weapons often rival the size of the skaven themselves. Their bulk is so prodigious that their use required two able-bodied skaven on the battlefield, one to hold the weapon itslef and the other to feed the ammunition into it. The designs used by your skaven are much more compact, much to their delight.</description>
		<baseCost>2000</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponsRanged_Skryre</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>5.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.0</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenPestilensWeaponry_Basic</defName>
		<label>Pestilens weaponry</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to make basic plague infused weaponry.\n\nEarly in their history, Clan Pestilens wanted a more immediate method of transferring their myriad plagues to the lizardmen of Lustria. Hoping that a plague monk would bleed enough on their killer to infect them wasn't quite fast enough or insidious enough. After some early failed designs, they came up with a method to bring diseased material with them into battle. Better yet, they found these censers could be weapons in their own right.</description>
		<baseCost>1000</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponryMelee_Improved</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>5.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenMoulderBio</defName>
		<label>Moulder bio-engineering</label>
		<description>Unlocks the next step in Moulder fleshcrafting, teaching your skaven how to create wolf rats from various canine test subjects.\n\nClan Moulder learned long ago that mixing a sample of skaven blood with some warpstone and injecting it into an animal could induce promising mutations. One of the earliest uses of this transfusion led to the creation of the first wolf rats, which the clan would later employ as sort of warhounds.</description>
		<baseCost>1750</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenMoulderBase</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>5.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_MagicIntermediate</defName>
		<label>Intermediate Magic Items</label>
		<description>Allows skaven seers to craft intermediate magic items.</description>
		<baseCost>3000</baseCost>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_Magic</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>5.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>5.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<!-- Column 7 -->
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenPestilensWeaponry_Advanced</defName>
		<label>Advanced Pestilens weaponry</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability to make improved plague censers.\n\nThe original designs for the plague censers of Clan Pestilens were crude and basic, rarely surviving more than a single battle. After they were cast out of Lustria by the lizardmen god Sotek, the clan further improved on this design by reinforcing the metal, adding spikes, and disease-riddled carrion to the censer itself. Later they also adjusted the design of the head itself to optimize the 'splash' of the pestilential fluid burning inside.</description>
		<baseCost>500</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenPestilensWeaponry_Basic</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>6.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenMoulderProsthetic</defName>
		<label>Moulder replacement body parts</label>
		<description>Unlocks the ability for the fleshcrafters of Clan Moulder to 'improve' the bodies of their fellow skaven by use of implanted warpstone.\n\nAfter learning the potential of fleshcraft, it's common for a Master Moulder to develop a god-complex. The ability to twist and bend the makeup of any creature's biology at a whim proves intoxicating, and it isn't long before they crave such 'improvements' for themself. Such operations are not without risk, but the payoff is worth more than a dozen warbeasts to the Master Moulders who do so.</description>
		<baseCost>2500</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenMoulderBase</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>6.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2.75</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_SkavenMoulderBioAdvanced</defName>
		<label>Advanced Moulder bio-engineering</label>
		<description>Unlocks the last step in Clan Moulder's twisted fleshcrafting arts, teaching your skaven how to create their own rat ogres.\n\nThe rat ogre is the most famous of Moulder's warbeasts, lacing skaven blood with ogre DNA to create an abomination of muscles and unrelenting rage. Since their inception the clan has tried to improve on these creatures, nailing plates of metal into their flesh or replacing their hands with warpstone prosthetics, but ultimately the rat ogre remained their most desired warbeast. It wouldn't be until the End-Times that Clan Moulder would truly innovate a replacement for these hulking monstrosities, meshing their fleshcraft with Skryre weaponry into a single monstrous being.</description>
		<baseCost>3000</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenMoulderBio</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>6.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_MagicAdvanced</defName>
		<label>Advanced Magic Items</label>
		<description>Allows skaven seers to craft advanced magic items.</description>
		<baseCost>3500</baseCost>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_MagicIntermediate</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>6.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>5.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<!-- Column 8 -->

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_MorskttarBasics</defName>
		<label>Morskittar Cannon</label>
		<description>Unlocks the creation of Skryre's most advanced weapon: the Morskittar Engine.\n\nThe End Times were rife with insanity, and the skaven Morskittar Engine was one such insanity that was brought into reality by the ingenous Warlock-Engineer Zingetail, this mighty machine is a titanic cannon which is meant to be aimed at the Chaos Moon itself, and when fired, to shatter it and allow warpstone meteorites to shower upon the world. This is the skaven plan to bring about the end of the civilized races, and finally show their superiority over all the other races of teh world.\n\nThe Morskittar Engine requires the cannon to be built, along with four supports, and a control box. It also requires additional power from the skaven batteries. Once everything is in place, the cannon can be started up. It will take 13 days to warm up before being capable of firing, during which time all manner of foes will attempt to destroy it. Once the cannon is fully charged, it can be fired, destroying the moon Morrslieb, raining copious amounts of warpstone upon the planet, and making the skaven victorious in their efforts.</description>
		<baseCost>13000</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_SkavenWeaponsRanged_SkryreAdvanced</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>7.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.0</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<!-- Column 9 -->

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_MorskttarPower</defName>
		<label>Morskittar Power</label>
		<description>Unlocks the creation of power cells to power the massive Clan Skryre Morskittar Engine.\n\nSeven of these power cells are required for The Device to fire, and they must be placed directly adjacent to it. They're more intricate, and more dangerous than the standard skaven battery, and cannot be used to power other devices.</description>
		<baseCost>2500</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_MorskttarBasics</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>8.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.0</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="RH_TET_Skaven_Research">
		<defName>RH_TET_Skaven_MorskttarControl</defName>
		<label>Morskittar Control</label>
		<description>Unlocks the creation of a control box that is required in order to use the massive Clan Skryre Morskittar Engine. Also unlocks the pawn surgery operation required to extract and preserve a living thinking brain.\n\nThe Device requires a single one of these, and one of the main components to create this must be created by performing an operation on a humanlike pawn.</description>
		<baseCost>5000</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<tags>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_ProjectTag</li>
		</tags>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RH_TET_Skaven_MorskttarBasics</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>8.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
  
  
</Defs>