<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Rimhammer - The End Times - Skaven</name>
	<author>SickBoyWI</author>
	<supportedVersions><li>1.5</li><li>1.6</li></supportedVersions>
	<packageId>SickBoyWi.TheEndTimes.Skaven</packageId>
	<description>
IF YOU HAVE ISSUES, YOU'LL GET A MUCH FASTER RESPONSE BY POSTING ON MY DISCORD ISSUES-AND-BUGS CHANNEL: https://discord.gg/UCmQbCT

This is the the fourth extension mod for the 'Rimhammer - The End Times' mod series, and is intended to be used with the base Rimhammer - The End Times mod; however, that isn't required.

Required mods (all must be loaded before this mod, and in this order [although other mods can fall inbetween or after these]):
Harmony
HugsLib
Vanilla Framework Expanded
SickTools
Humanoid Alien Races 2.0
Rimhammer - The End Times [Optional]
Rimhammer - The End Times - Magic

The Rimhammer mods should be placed at the bottom of your mod list. Place the base Rimhammer - The End Times mod at the bottom, then the Rimhammer - Then End Times - Magic mod, then the race/faction mods under those.

This mod adds Warhammer themed The Skaven into Rimworld.

A detailed list of things this extension adds are as follows:
	-Research, warpstone, warpstone powder, custom furniture, floors, statues, doors, wall lights, walls, many different types of skaven, backstories, warmachines (warplightning cannon, jezzails), apparel (armor, shirts, pants, helmets, headgear, ...), mshields, recreation, indoor planter box, plants (black corn), feed hoppers, unique food types, names, weapons (melee, ranged, massive ranged, ...), custom work and research benches, a unique end game quest, animals (rat ogres, rat wolfs), surgeries / operations for creating the new animals, skaven screaming bell, Morskittar Engine, and more!

Special Thanks To:
	-Kompad for graciously letting me start with his skaven mod, and flesh it out to what this is.
	-Discord member @Dino's Bar and Grill for his amazing textures!
	-BlackRussian on Discord for the amazing help on gathering info for the skaven specific magic spells.
	-The Family God on Discord for fluff on most everything.
	-All the Discord members who helped out with testing.
	
This series will likely not be released fast. I'm one person, and the amount of work involved is significant. This mod took hundreds, perhaps thousands, hours of work, no joke. It was over 11 months of work for me.

If you'd like to speed up the process of release, please consider supporting me on Patreon. The more support I get, the more motivated I will be to create more races/factions. https://www.patreon.com/SickBoyWI	

Buy me a coffee: https://ko-fi.com/sickboywi

Join the Discord channel: https://discord.gg/UCmQbCT

========================
Changelog
========================

0.0.0.1 2021-01-24
========================
Development started. 
	</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
			<displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl />
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl />
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>zal.brawlerfriendly</packageId>
			<displayName>Brawler-Friendly</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3510865756</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl />
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>sickboywi.sicktools</packageId>
			<displayName>SickTools</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=3221151657</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl />
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
			<displayName>Humanoid Alien Races</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl />
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>SickBoyWi.TheEndTimes.Magic</packageId>
			<displayName>Rimhammer - The End Times - Magic</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2020384442</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl />
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.BioTech</li>
		<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
		<li>sickboywi.sicktools</li>
		<li>jecrell.doorsexpanded</li>
		<li>SickBoyWi.TheEndTimes.Magic</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>